Margaret Henderson Floyd Architectural Slide Collection MS175
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Architectural slides, 1955 -- 1998; 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001; 16.0 Linear Feet
  - Central American, South American, US, and Spanish architecture, 1955 -- 1997; MS175.001.018
    - Puebla, Mexico / Cathedral, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00014 (Box 36)
    - Puebla, Mexico / Church of Santo Domingo, Rosary Chapel (Capillo del Rosario), 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00015 (Box 36)
    - Puebla, Mexico. Misc. Houses, 1956 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00016 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete Arcade, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00017 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete opp. Arcade [1], 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00018 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete opp. Arcade [2], 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00019 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete opp. Arcade, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00020 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete La Parroquia San Juan, Bautista, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00021 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete La Parroquia San Juan, Bautista, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00022 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete La Parroquia San Juan, Bautista, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00023 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete La Parroquia San Juan, Bautista, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00024 (Box 36)
    - (Sept. Mexico) Sombrerete, 1993; MS175.001.036.00025 (Box 36)
    - (Sept. Mexico) Sombrerete, 1993; MS175.001.036.00026 (Box 36)
    - (Sept. Mexico) Sombrerete, 1993; MS175.001.036.00027 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00028 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete Interiors, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00029 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete. Blue Walls, round dome, round upper window, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00030 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00031 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete, Interior, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00032 (Box 36)
    - Sombrerete, Interiors, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00033 (Box 36)
    - M. Lehner. Taxco, Mexico, MS175.001.036.00034 (Box 36)
      Date is unknown.
      M. Lehner
    - Taxco, Mexico. Santa Prisca, 1978 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00035 (Box 36)
    - Peru, 1979; MS175.001.036.00036 (Box 36)
    - Cordoba, Spain / Marque (la meszquita), 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00037 (Box 36)
    - Granada, Spain. Alhambra, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00038 (Box 36)
    - Texas Missions, San Antonio/San Jose (Huilar), 1978; MS175.001.036.00039 (Box 36)
    - Texas Missions, San Antonio, 1978; MS175.001.036.00040 (Box 36)
    - Texas, San Antonio. Governor's Palace, MS175.001.036.00041 (Box 36)
  - Italian architects, 1977 -- 1997; MS175.001.019
    - Inventory, 1996 -- 1997; MS175.001.037.00001 (Box 37)
    - Leon Battista Alberti / Basilica di Sant'Andrea / San Sebastiano, 1977; MS175.001.037.00002 (Box 37)
      Alberti, Leon Battista, 1404-1472
    - Giuseppe Mengoni, 1977; MS175.001.037.00003 (Box 37)
      Mengoni, Giuseppe, 1829-1877
    - Luigi Voghera, 1977; MS175.001.037.00004 (Box 37)
      Voghera, Luigi, 1788-1840
    - Andrea Palladio, 1977; MS175.001.037.00005 (Box 37)
      Palladio, Andrea, 1508-1580
    - Giulio Romano / Palazzo del Te, 1977; MS175.001.037.00006 (Box 37)
      Romano, Giulio, 1499-1546
    - Giulio Romano / Palace of Justice [Palazzo della Raggione] / House of G. Romano, 1977; MS175.001.037.00007 (Box 37)
    - Michele Sanmicheli, 1977; MS175.001.037.00008 (Box 37)
      Sanmicheli, Michele
    - Jacopo Sansovino, 1977; MS175.001.037.00009 (Box 37)
      Sansovino, Jacopo, 1486-1570
    - Francesco Sforza, 1977; MS175.001.037.00010 (Box 37)
      Sforza, Francesco, Duke of Milan, 1401-1466
    - Ulisse Stacchini, 1977; MS175.001.037.00011 (Box 37)
      Stacchini, Ulisse, 1871-1947
  - Terra cotta, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.020
    - Inventory, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.038.00001 (Box 38)
    - Hathernware [1], 1981; MS175.001.038.00002 (Box 38)
    - Hathernware [2], 1981; MS175.001.038.00003 (Box 38)
    - Hathernware [3], 1981; MS175.001.038.00004 (Box 38)
    - Chabat, Pierre, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.038.00005 (Box 38)
      Chabat, Pierre, 1827-1892
    - Gruner/Humbert/Runge, 1971; MS175.001.038.00006 (Box 38)
      Gruner, Ludwig, 1801-1882; Humbert, Albert Jenkins
    - Salviati, Antonio, 1990; MS175.001.038.00007 (Box 38)
      Salviati, Antonio, 1816-1890
    - Terra Cotta [2], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.038.00008 (Box 38)
    - Terra Cotta [4], 1972 -- 1981; MS175.001.038.00009 (Box 38)
      Some slides are missing as of 2010-11-22. Dates are approximate.
    - Miscellaneous Drawings, 1972; MS175.001.038.00010 (Box 38)
      Daly, Cesar, 1811-1893
    - See Bank in Stratford-Avon, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.038.00011 (Box 38)
    - England 19th century China, 1971; MS175.001.038.00012 (Box 38)
  - Painting and scultpure, 1969 -- 1997; MS175.001.021
    - Inventory, 1990 -- 1997; MS175.001.039.00001 (Box 39)
    - Portraits, 1975 -- 1976; MS175.001.039.00002 (Box 39)
    - E.A. Abbey, 1972 -- 1974; MS175.001.039.00003 (Box 39)
      Abbey, Edwin Austin, 1852-1911
    - W. Allston, 1973; MS175.001.039.00004 (Box 39)
      Allston, Washington, 1779-1843
    - Bierstadt, 1973; MS175.001.039.00005 (Box 39)
      Bierstadt, Albert, 1830-1902
    - E. Blashfield / D.G. Blythe, 1973 -- 1974; MS175.001.039.00006 (Box 39)
      Blashfield, Edwin Howland, 1848-1936; Blythe, David Gilmour, 1815-1865
    - Puvis de Chavannes, 1975; MS175.001.039.00007 (Box 39)
      De Chavannes, Pierre Puvis, 1824-1898
    - Thomas Cole, 1973; MS175.001.039.00008 (Box 39)
      Cole, Thomas, 1801-1848
    - Benjamin Constant #1 / Murals at Ames-Webster House, 1975; MS175.001.039.00009 (Box 39)
      Benjamin-Constant, Jean Joseph, 1845-1902
    - Benjamin Constant #2, 1975; MS175.001.039.00010 (Box 39)
    - A.B. Durand, 1970 -- 1990; MS175.001.039.00011 (Box 39)
      Durand, Asher Brown, 1796-1886
    - Gérôme / Harnett, 1975; MS175.001.039.00012 (Box 39)
      G&#00E9;r&#00F4;me, Jean L&#00E9;on, 1824-1904; Harnett, William Michael, 1848-1892
    - Wm. Hunt / S.F. Morse, 1973; MS175.001.039.00013 (Box 39)
      Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 1791-1872; Hunt, William Morris, 1824-1879
    - J. LaFarge, 1973 -- 1979; MS175.001.039.00014 (Box 39)
      LaFarge, John, 1835-1910
    - Rosetti, 1970 -- 1990; MS175.001.039.00015 (Box 39)
      Rosetti, Dante Gabriel, 1828-1882
    - J.S. Sargent, 1973 -- 1974; MS175.001.039.00016 (Box 39)
      Sargent, John Singer, 1856-1925
    - Moyr Smith, 1972; MS175.001.039.00017 (Box 39)
      Moyr Smith, John, 1839-1912
    - A. Thayer / Caritas, 1973; MS175.001.039.00018 (Box 39)
      Thayer, Abbott Handerson, 1849-1921
    - R. Weir, 1970 -- 1990; MS175.001.039.00019 (Box 39)
      Weir, Robert Walter, 1803-1889
    - B. West, 1973; MS175.001.039.00020 (Box 39)
      West, Benjamin, 1738-1820
    - J.M. Whistler, 1970; MS175.001.039.00021 (Box 39)
      Whistler, James McNeill, 1834-1903
    - Th. Crawford, 1970; MS175.001.039.00022 (Box 39)
      Crawford, Thomas, 1813 or 14-1857
    - Dengler / Duveneck / Daniel Chester French, 1973 -- 1979; MS175.001.039.00023 (Box 39)
      Dengler, Francis (1853-1879); Duveneck, Frank, 1848-1919; French, Daniel Chester, 1850-1931
    - Th. Gould / Greenough / see portrait by H. Powers, 1973; MS175.001.039.00024 (Box 39)
      Gould, Thomas Ridgeway, 1818-1881; Greenough, Horatio, 1805-1852
    - H. Hosmer / Kitson, 1973; MS175.001.039.00025 (Box 39)
      Hosmer, Harriet Goodhue, 1830-1908; Kitson, Henry Hudson, 1863?-1947
    - [Orozco], 1979; MS175.001.039.00026 (Box 39)
      Orozco, Jos&#00E9; Clemente, 1883-1949
    - H. Powers / MacMonnies, 1973; MS175.001.039.00027 (Box 39)
      Powers, Hiram, 1805-1873; MacMonnies, Frederick William, 1863-1937
    - W. Rimmer, 1973; MS175.001.039.00028 (Box 39)
      Rimmer, William, 1816-1879
    - Rosenthal / F. Simmons / Wm. Storey, 1973; MS175.001.039.00029 (Box 39)
      Rosenthal, Toby Edward, ca. 1848-1917; Simmons, Franklin, 1839-1913; Story, William Wetmore, 1819-1895
    - E. Thaxter, 1973; MS175.001.039.00030 (Box 39)
      Thaxter, Edward
    - Stained glass Burne-Jones, 1969 -- 1979; MS175.001.039.00031 (Box 39)
      Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, 1833-1898
    - Stained glass Trinity Church Boston / Tiffany, 1969 -- 1979; MS175.001.039.00032 (Box 39)
    - S. Whitman, 1976; MS175.001.039.00033 (Box 39)
      Whitman, Sarah Helen, 1803-1878
    - MFA Confident America, 1973; MS175.001.039.00034 (Box 39)
  - Colling, James Kellaway, 1996 -- 1997; MS175.001.022
    - Inventory, 1996 -- 1997; MS175.001.040.00001 (Box 40)
    - The Albany, Old Hall Street, Liverpool, 1997; MS175.001.040.00002 (Box 40)
    - Eastham, 1997; MS175.001.040.00003 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall, 1997; MS175.001.040.00004 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall, 1997; MS175.001.040.00005 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall - new banqueting room or sculpture gallery, 1997; MS175.001.040.00006 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall - new banqueting room or sculpture gallery, 1997; MS175.001.040.00007 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall, 1997; MS175.001.040.00008 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall conservatory, 1997; MS175.001.040.00009 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall new sculpture gallery, 1997; MS175.001.040.00010 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall Chapel, 1997; MS175.001.040.00011 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall- tower addition and rooms, 1997; MS175.001.040.00012 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall- entrance, 1997; MS175.001.040.00013 (Box 40)
    - Hooton Hall- plans, 1997; MS175.001.040.00014 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [postcard], 1997; MS175.001.040.00015 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton, 1997; MS175.001.040.00016 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [exterior], 1997; MS175.001.040.00017 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton, 1997; MS175.001.040.00018 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton, 1997; MS175.001.040.00019 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [interior], 1997; MS175.001.040.00020 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [interior details], 1997; MS175.001.040.00021 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [interior details], 1997; MS175.001.040.00022 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [interior details], 1997; MS175.001.040.00023 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [statuary and interior details], 1997; MS175.001.040.00024 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [column details], 1997; MS175.001.040.00025 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [column details], 1997; MS175.001.040.00026 (Box 40)
    - St. Paul's - Hooton [column details], 1997; MS175.001.040.00027 (Box 40)
    - Kelmarsh, 1997; MS175.001.040.00028 (Box 40)